appzone.com 2013-08-05

# AppZone > Terms&Privacy > Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement**

AppZone is committed to protecting the privacy of all of our customers and visitors to the highest industry standards and to using technology that provides an exceptional, intuitive, and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the AppZone website and related services and governs data collection and usage. By using the AppZone website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

AppZone complies with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.  Information regarding the EU Safe Harbor Framework can be found at: <http://export.gov/safeharbor>

**Collection of your Personal Information  
**

AppZone collects personal information (including personally identifiable information) from you on the registration form when you create an account. This information might include, but may not be limited to, your e-mail address, name, home and/or work address, home and/or work telephone number, and credit card information. We also collect your personal information when you contact us (e.g., sales/product inquiries, technical support). We use this information to communicate with you. AppZone may also collect anonymous information such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests, and favorites for market research. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by AppZone. This information may include, but is not necessarily limited to, your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. Collectively, this information is used by AppZone for the delivery and/or operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide both specific and anonymous statistics regarding use of the AppZone website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personal information or personally sensitive data through AppZone websites or services hosted on AppZone.com or its subdomains, this information may be collected and used by others. To request removal of your personal information from our website, contact us at: support@AppZone.com.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

AppZone encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from AppZone so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share information. AppZone is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the AppZone family of websites.

**Use of Your Personal Information  
**

**General**  
AppZone collects and uses your personal information to operate the AppZone website and deliver the services you have requested. AppZone also uses your personal information to inform you of other products or services that may be available from AppZone and/or its affiliates. 

AppZone may also post surveys to our website or contact you regarding surveys. We use surveys to better understand our customers, to provide higher quality services, to conduct market research, and to provide guidance to the products and services we offer, among other things. AppZone may also conduct contests or promotions from time to time. If you participate in any contest, promotion, or survey we may request certain personal information from you. Participation in any survey or contest is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether to participate. By participating in any contest, survey, and/or promotion you consent to the use of any information you provide, at the sole judgment of AppZone.  AppZone may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys, contests, and/or promotions. Any third party service provider will be prohibited from using the information for any other purpose.  We will not share the personal information you provide through a contest, survey, or promotion with any outside individual or organization for any unrelated purpose except as provided herein.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide services to you.  If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us via email at: support@AppZone.com. In the sole judgment of AppZone, we may retain and use your information indefinitely to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, maintain business records, support client sales and/or service histories, or as otherwise in the normal course of business.

**Testimonials**  
We post customer testimonials, statements, and/or other similar items (collectively “Testimonial” or “Testimonials”) on our website which may contain personally identifiable information.  Generally, we obtain the customer’s consent via email prior to posting the Testimonial.  To request removal of your personal information from our Testimonials, please contact us at support@AppZone.com.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.  

**Special Offers and Updates**  
We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special promotions, and other marketing communications as part of being a customer of AppZone.  If you do not wish to receive these emails, you may deactivate your account. 

**Newsletters**  
We will use your personal information to send a newsletter or other updates to you.  Receiving our newsletter and/or update are required as part of the service that we offer.  If you wish to no longer receive our newsletters you may deactivate your account.

**Service-Related Announcements**  
We will send you service-related announcements when it is necessary to do so.  Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications since they are directly related to the delivery of products and services you have requested.  If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

**Restrictions and Limitations**  

AppZone does not sell, rent, or lease its customer lists to third parties. AppZone may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information will not be transferred to the third party. In addition, AppZone may share data with trusted third parties to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, arrange for deliveries, process credit card payments, provide customer support, provide additional support via Live Chat to assist you if you have questions while using our site, or regarding your order. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information in any way other than in a manner directly applicable to providing these services to you and AppZone and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

AppZone does not collect, use, or disclose certain sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

**Legal Compliance**  
AppZone websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on AppZone or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of AppZone; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety or property of AppZone site visitors, AppZone, AppZone customers, or the public.

**Choice/Opt-out**  

AppZone may provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personal information used for certain purposes, excepting those required herein. To the best of our ability, you will be notified and allowed to make an informed choice whether your personal information should be shared with any unrelated third party individual or organization. 

**Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information**  
If you need to update your personal information you may make these changes at any time through the online control panel provided to you. Ensuring that your information is up to date and accurate is important and your responsibility. If you need assistance with updating your information, contact us via email at: [support@AppZone.com](mailto:support@AppZone.com)

**Use of Cookies**  
The AppZone website uses "cookies" to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a website. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize AppZone pages or register with AppZone site or services, a cookie helps AppZone to recall specific information and details on subsequent visits to make the site faster and more convenient, among other things.  

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the AppZone services or websites you visit.

The use of cookies by any third party is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access to or control over these cookies.

**Security of your Personal Information  
**

AppZone maintains the information you provide in a controlled, secure environment, protected to industry standards from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted over the internet, it is protected through the use of encryption (e.g., Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol).

**Changes to this Statement  
**

AppZone reserves the right to update this Statement of Privacy at any time, with or without notice. _This Statement of Privacy is important and affects your rights and responsibilities, so please review it frequently_. 

**Contact Information**  
If you have questions or comments regarding this statement or believe that information has been handled in a manner inconsistent with the provisions herein, please contact AppZone at: [support@AppZone.com](mailto:support@AppZone.com)
